Patryk Kiełsa

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Profile

I'm an enthusiastic Software Engineer with a proactive attitude and talent for problem solving. Having experience with procedural, functional and object oriented programming paradigms, I have worked extensively with many modern technologies including Python, JavaScript, AWS Services, Terraform and Node.js. I'm comfortable working in cross-functional teams using Agile development and modern code review practices.

After 9 years in the United Kingdom I'm looking for a company in Poland which I can help to develop top tier software solutions by applying my skills and passion for tech.

Employment History

Junior Software Engineer, Hippo Digital, Remote

NOVEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with an Agile team, participating in daily standups, Three Amigos sessions, sprint planning while developing software solutions iteratively.
- Created **data integration** projects for clients, being involved in the process from the design stage to deployment and beyond.
- Worked with Python, JavaScript, AWS, Terraform and more.
- Adjusted software designs to incorporate new features into projects and used facts and best practice to suggest improvements in the code base.
- Used both manual and unit testing to ensure robustness of the code.
- Investigated and fixed bugs in Dev, UAT and Production environments.

Software Developer, Freelance, Bristol

AUGUST 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

- Developed clear specifications for project plans using pre-determined requirements.
- Integrated third-party tools (e.g. Google Maps API, AWS Cognito) into applications.
- Worked with Svelte, React and Typescript.

Delivery Driver, Amazon Logistics, Bristol

APRIL 2020 - JANUARY 2022

Event Manager/Content Manager, Prysm Group, Bristol

JUNE 2018 - FEBRUARY 2020

Education

Intensive Fullstack Developer Bootcamp, School of Code, Birmingham

APRIL 2022 – AUGUST 2022

Business and Events Management, BSc, University of the West of England, Bristol

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2018

Courses

Deep Dive with Security: AWS IAM, AWS

AWS Partner: Accreditation (Technical), AWS

C++ for Programmers, Online Course, Codecademy

 $\label{lem:build} \textbf{Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS}, \textbf{Online Course}, \textbf{Udemy}$

Details

Warsaw Poland 881 955 874 <u>kielsa.patryk@gmail.com</u>

Links

Portfolio

Github

LinkedIn

Technologies

Python

JavaScript

Typescript

PostgreSQL

C++

AWS

Terraform

Next.js

Node.js

Frameworks: React, Svelte
Testing: Postman, Jest, Pytest,
Cypress

Skills

Problem Solving
Collaborative Programming
Agile Development
Excellent Communication Skills
Attention to detail

Languages

English

Polish

Spanish